worldawide.com 2011-12-19

# Privacy policy - www.worldawide.com

Worldawide.com respects the privacy and security of its users. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from each of our millions of other users.

In order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing the privacy practices for the entire Worldawide.com site. Additional terms and conditions, if any, regarding the collection and use of your information may also be provided to you before you sign up for a particular service (like My Worldawide.com). Here, you will learn what personally identifiable information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

What Information is Collected:

Worldawide.com collects certain information from and about its users in three ways -- directly from the user, from our Web server logs, and with cookies.

User-Supplied Information: When you sign up for a service, such as a Newsletter or My Worldawide.com, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, zip code and some other personal information. The more accurate information you volunteer, the better we are able to customize your Worldawide.com experience.

Server Log Information: When you visit an Internet Web site, you disclose certain information about yourself, such as your Internet [Protocol] (IP) address, the time of your visit, and the referring location (e.g., the Site or page that offered a link to a Worldawide.com page). Worldawide.com, like many other sites, records this basic information about visits to its site.

Cookies: In order to offer and provide a customized, personal service, Worldawide.com may use cookies to store and help track your information. For example, we may use cookies to help remind us who you are and to deliver content and services based on your account information. In addition, third party advertising networks may issue cookies when serving advertisements.

Cookies are simply pieces of information that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. The use of cookies is relatively standard and you will likely find them used on most other major Web sites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that certain areas of many sites may not function properly if you set your browser to not accept cookies or if you reject a cookie.

You should remember that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, such as on message boards, through e-mail, discussion groups, or in chat areas, your information can be collected and used by others. Although Worldawide.com tries to protect your personal information, Worldawide.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. You are also solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords you set up and/or any account information.
